<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Couponsonakeychain.com]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Couponsonakeychain.com]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 15:54:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Burrito Boyz In my 34 years of making coupons for clients, NEVER have I had such a great response from consumers about a food coupon. And that coupon is: Ta-Da! Burrito Boyz. The comments I’ve gotten are incredible to say the least; such as: It’s the “best Burrito there is” It’s “really big and filling” “Huge” “Fantastic” “Awesome” about 50 times. “Since I tasted my first Burrito Boyz it’s the only Burrito I eat” “Burrito Boyz or nothing else” I think you get the idea. What more can I really write after these comments? So you can take the word of literally dozens of consumers who’ve raved about this fantastic product! You can save up to $5.00 or up to 50% off on a Burrito Boyz burrito. Or you can have a free salsa with chips when you buy a Burrito Boyz burrito. Save $2.00 701 Wonderland Rd N. 206 Central Ave. Eat-in or Take-out. Buy Coupons on a Key Chain at these locations. Jumbo Video at Adelaide @ Huron, The Water Store at Wellington @ Baseline, Fanshawe Mini Mart Oxford @ 2nd next to Fanshawe College, Toner Tech 1724 Hyde Park, Rundle’s No Frills 635 Southdale Rd East, United Supermarket on Adelaide, Hyde Park Computers on Hyde Park, Pause Cafe @ 111 Waterloo St, Campus Hi-Fi @ Richmond @ Oxford, AK Arts Academy @ Hyde Park @ Fanshawe Park, Winexpert @ Waterloo @ Piccadilly. Please note: Rundle’s No Frills has our biggest supply of our newest coupon book with Burrito Boyz inside. Stores that have Newest books also are United Supermarket, and Jumbo Video. Thanks for shopping Coupons on a Key Chain………………Michael only $5 good for 2 years.</p>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedburrito-boyz-in-my-34-years-of-making-coupons-for-clients-n/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">45258f44-2db7-43f9-9bc5-23b8c1dfeff0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 15:54:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>